Guide to the Gotham Inc. Records, 1967-1997 and undated RL.00468
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Audiovisual Materials, 1973-1996 and undated, 129 boxes
  - Major Clients, 1973-1996 and undated
    - Bristol Myers, 1973-1996 and undated
      - Bufferin (continued), 1987 (Box 21)
        - 338. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol-Myers. Bufferin. BMBU 7155 AHA/Bufferin Shield :15. 1987 (Box 21)
        - 339. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol-Myers. Tri-Buffered Bufferin. 6-30 Sec. Spots. See Enclosed List. 1987 (Box 21)
        - 340. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol-Myers. Bufferin. BMBU 7193 Geoff Kimbell/ABC :30. 1987 (Box 21)
        - 341. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol-Myers. Extra Strength Bufferin. Class Reunion: BMBX6123 :30, BMBX 6135 :15. 1987 (Box 21)
        - 342. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol-Myers. Bufferin. 4 Spots. See Enclosed List. 1987 (Box 21)
        - 343. Boclard. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol-Myers. AHA Bufferin. 6-60 Sec. Spots. See Enclosed List. 1987 (Box 21)
      - Bufferin (continued), 1987-1988 (Box 22)
        - 344. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol-Myers. 4-30 Sec. Spots. See Enclosed List. 1987 (Box 22)
        - 345. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol-Myers. Bufferin. BMBU 7173 Geoff Kimbell :30; AHA Bufferin Shield :45 :15 Without Heartbeat. Undated (Box 22)
        - 346. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol-Myers. Tri-Buffered Bufferin. BMBI 7103 Aspirin You Can Stomach :30. 1987 (Box 22)
        - 347. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol-Myers. Bufferin. BMBU 7205 AHA Bufferin Shield Rev. :15. 1987 (Box 22)
        - 348. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Tri-Buffered Bufferin. 10-30 Sec. Spots. See Enclosed List. 1987 (Box 22)
        - 349. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol-Myers. Bufferin. BMBX 7163 Class Reunion AHA Tag :30. 1987 (Box 22)
        - 350. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol-Myers. Tri-Buffered Bufferin. BMBI 7113 Real People w/c.g. Copy-Women End V.O. Levine Music :30. 1987 (Box 22)
        - 351. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol-Myers. Bufferin. BMBU 8303 Winner Revised/Buffered Everyday :30. 1988 (Box 22)
        - 352. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol-Myers. Tri-Buffered Bufferin. BMBU 8613 Flipping Pages-Aches & Pains Rev. 2 :30. 1988 (Box 22)
        - 353. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol-Myers. Tri-Buffered Bufferin. BMBU 8523 Flipping Pages/Aches & Pains Rev. 1 :30. 1988 (Box 22)
        - 354. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol-Myers. Tri-Buffered Bufferin. BMBU 8693 Flipping Pages/Aches & Pains Non-New :30; BMBU 8663 Flipping Pages/Man NON-New :30. 1988 (Box 22)
        - 355. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bufferin. 4-30 Sec. Spots. See Enclosed List. 1988 (Box 22)
        - 356. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol-Myers. Tri-Buffered Bufferin. BMBU 8263 Calendar :30. 1988 (Box 22)
        - 357. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bufferin. Picnic":30; BMBU 8303"Winning Rev./Buffered Everyday :30; BMBU 8623 Flipping Pages/Man Rev. :30. 1988 (Box 22)
        - 358. DJM. Bristol-Myers. Tri-Buffered Bufferin. BMBU 8583 Flipping Pages/Man Rev.4; BMBU 8593 Flipping pages/ Man Rev. 5; BMBU 8603 Flipping Pages/Headache Rev.5 :30 Each. 1988 (Box 22)
        - 359. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol-Myers. Bufferin. BMBU 8243 Arthur Ash-Winner Rev :30; BMBU 8253 Arthur Ashe-winner Rev (Everyday) :30. 1988 (Box 22)
        - 360. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol-Myers. Tri-Buffered Bufferin. BMBU 8383 TBB Workout :30. 1988 (Box 22)
      - Bufferin (continued), 1988-1989 (Box 23)
        - 361. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol-Myers. Tri-Buffered Bufferin. BMBU 8603 Flipping Pages/Headache Rev. 5 :30; BMBU 8613 Flipping Pages/Aches & Pains Rev. 2 :30; BMBU 8623 Flipping Pages/Man Rev. :30. 1988 (Box 23)
        - 362. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol-Myers. Bufferin. BMBU 7173 Geoff Kimbell :30; BMBU 7183 Geoff Kimball/NBC Rev. :30; BMBU 7193 Geoff Kimball/ABC :30. 1988 (Box 23)
        - 363. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bufferin. BMBU 8373 TRI-Buffered Bufferin TBB Intro :30; BMBU 8383 TBB Workout :30. 1988 (Box 23)
        - 364. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol-Myers. Bufferin. BMBU 8253 Arthur Ashe-Winner rev/Everyday :30. 1988 (Box 23)
        - 365. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol-Myers. Bufferin. BMBU 8253 Ashe-winner Rev. everyday :30; BMBU 8293 Winner Rev./Buffered :30; BMBU 8303 winner Rev./Buffered Everyday :30. 1988 (Box 23)
        - 366. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol-Myers. Bufferin. BMBU 8703 1800A Bufferin Man :30; BMBU 8703 1800 A Buffering Man Alt. :30. 1988 (Box 23)
        - 367. DJM. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol-Myers. Tri-Buffered Bufferin. BMBU 8523 Flipping Pages/Aches&Pains Rev. 1 :30. 1988 (Box 23)
        - 368. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol-Myers. Bufferin. BMBU 8293 Winner Rev. /Buffered :30. 1988 (Box 23)
        - 369. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol-Myers. Tri-Buffered Bufferin. Snapshots 8 Spots. See Enclosed List. 1989 (Box 23)
        - 370. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bufferin. BMBU 8703 1800A Bufferin Man Alt. Rev. :30. 1989 (Box 23)
        - 371. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bufferin. Demo Spot I Can Do Rev. :30. 1989 (Box 23)
        - 372. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bufferin. Demo Spot Bowl Of Cherries :30. 1989 (Box 23)
        - 373. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol-Myers. Tri-Buffered Bufferin. 6 Spots. See Enclosed List. 1989 (Box 23)
        - 374. DJM. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Tri-Buffered Bufferin. BMBU 9533 Lansbury A Cup of Tea :30; BMBU 9553 Lansbury c Advice :30. 1989 (Box 23)
        - 375. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol-Myers. Tri-Buffered Bufferin. 8-30 Sec. Spots. See Enclosed List. 1989 (Box 23)
        - 376. Laurence Charles and Free. Bristol-Myers. Tri-Buffered Bufferin. BMBU 9213 MI Rev. :30; BMBU 9225 MI Rev. 2 :15; BMBU 9235 MI Monday Rev. 2 :15. 1989 (Box 23)
        - 377. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol-Myers. Tri-Buffered Bufferin. 6-30Sec. Spots. See Enclosed List. 1989 (Box 23)
      - Bufferin (continued), 1989-1991 (Box 24)
        - 378. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol-Myers. Tri-Buffered Bufferin. 4-30 Sec. Spots. See Enclosed List. 1989 (Box 24)
        - 379. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol-Myers. Snap Shots. 6-15 Sec. Spots. See Enclosed List. Undated (Box 24)
        - 380. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bufferin. I Can Do :30 Demo Spot. 1989 (Box 24)
        - 381. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bufferin The Glass Man :30. 1989 (Box 24)
        - 382. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol-Myers. Tri-Buffered Bufferin. Dailies Of Man 22000 Super 60 Min. 1989 (Box 24)
        - 383. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol-Myers. Tri-Buffered Bufferin. Angela Lansbury Interview Alt :30. 1989 (Box 24)
        - 384. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bufferin. BMBU 8633 Man Review 7 :30. 1989 (Box 24)
        - 385. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol-Myers. Tri-Buffered Bufferin. Snap Shots. BMBU 9213 MI Rev. 2 :30; BMBU 9225 MI Rev. 2 :15; BMBU 9235 MI Monday Rev. 2 :15. 1989 (Box 24)
        - 386. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol-Myers. Tri-Buffered Bufferin. Snap Shot. BMBU 9373 Monday Core Rev. :30; BMBU 9383 Thursday Core Rev. :30; BMBU 9393 Friday Core Rev. :30. 1989 (Box 24)
        - 387. DJM. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Tri-Buffered Bufferin. BMBU 9533 Lansbury A cup of Tea :30; BMBU 9553 Lansbury C/Advice :30. 1989 (Box 24)
        - 388. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bufferin. 4-30 Sec. Spots. See Enclosed List. 1989 (Box 24)
        - 389. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol-Myers. Bufferin. True of False/Male Demo; True of False/Female Demo; True of False/Female Alt. Demo. 1989 (Box 24)
        - 390. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol-Myers. Tri-Buffered Bufferin. BMBU 0843 Lansbury/Library Rev. 4 :30. 1990 (Box 24)
        - 391. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol-Myers. Tri-Buffered Bufferin. BMBU 0823 Lansbury/Library Rev. 2 :30. 1990 (Box 24)
        - 392. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol-Myers. Tri-Buffered Bufferin. BMBU9663 Rosebush Alt. :30; BMBU 9673 Girl :30; BMBU 9683 Wisdom :30. 1990 (Box 24)
        - 393. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol-Myers. Extra Strength Bufferin. 5-30 Sec. Spots. See Enclosed List. 1990 (Box 24)
        - 394. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol-Myers. Bufferin AF Nighttime. BMBG 1053 Something New Rev. :30. 1991 (Box 24)
      - Bufferin (continued), 1991-1993 and Undated (Box 25)
        - 395. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Extra Strength Bufferin. BMBX 1343 Ask Angela/Headache :30; BMBX 1353 Ask Angela/Backache :30. 1991 (Box 25)
        - 396. Daniel & Charles. Bristol Myers. Extra Strength Bufferin. 5 Spots. See Enclosed List. Undated (Box 25)
        - 397. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers Squibb. Extra Strength Bufferin. Already :30. 1991 (Box 25)
        - 398. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson.Extra Strength Bufferin. BMBX 1363 Angela/Letters, Split Screen :30; BMBX 1383 Angela/Letters, Living Room Ver. B Rev. :30. 1991 (Box 25)
        - 399. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers Squibb. Extra Strength Bufferin. 6 Spots. See Enclosed List. 1991 (Box 25)
        - 400. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bufferin. 4 Spots. See Enclosed List. 1992 (Box 25)
        - 401. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bufferin Reel #1. 29 Spots. See Enclosed list. 1992 (Box 25)
        - 402. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers Squibb. Extra Strength Bufferin. BMBX 2753 Angela/Moving Rev. 2 :30; BMBX 2745 Angela/Moving Rev. :15; Bufferin Line. BMBI 2283 Angela/Moving w/Tag Rev. 2 :30;. 1992 (Box 25)
        - 403. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson.Bristol Myers Squibb. Bufferin Af Nighttime. BMBG 1053 Angela AF/Something New Rev. :30; BMBG 1063 Angela AF/Something New Rev. (Non-New) :30. 1992 (Box 25)
        - 404. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers Squibb. Extra Strength Bufferin. BMBX 1443 Ask Angela/Couples :30. 1992 (Box 25)
        - 405. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers Squibb. Bufferin Line. BMBI 2293 Angela/Moving w/Tag Rev. 3 :30. 1992 (Box 25)
        - 406. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers Squibb. Bufferin Line. 4 Spots. See Enclosed List. 1992 (Box 25)
        - 407. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson.Bristol Myers Squibb. Extra Strength Bufferin. 4 spots. See Enclosed List. 1992 (Box 25)
        - 408. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson.Bristol Myers Squibb. Tri-Buffered Bufferin. BMBU 9533 Lansbury A/Cup of Tea :30. 1993 (Box 25)
        - 409. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson.Bufferin. 13 Spots. See Enclosed List. 1992 (Box 25)
        - 410. Bufferin Line. Hobby Painter :30. Type :30. Undated (Box 25)
        - 411. Bufferin Line. Hobby Painter :30. Type :30. Undated (Box 25)
      - Comtrex, 1976-1979 (Box 26)
        - 412. Daniel & Charles. Comtrex. BMCE 6093 Couple Rev. #3 Version ABC and CBS. Undated (Box 26)
        - 413. Daniel & Charles. Comtrex. BMCE 6103 Couple Rev. #5 :30. 1976 (Box 26)
        - 414. Comtrex. BMCE 6083 Check Rev. #2, New Audio. 1976 (Box 26)
        - 415. Daniel & Charles. Comtrex. BMCE 6053 Worst Rev. :30; BMCE 6043 Check Rev. :30; BMCE 6063 Couple Rev. :30. 1976 (Box 26)
        - 416. Comtrex. BMCE 6103 Couple rev. #4. 1976 (Box 26)
        - 417. Daniel & Charles. Bristol Myers. Comtrex. BMCE 6123 Couple Re. #6 :30. 1976 (Box 26)
        - 418. Comtrex. BMCE7133 Check Rev. #3. 1977 (Box 26)
        - 419. Daniel & Charles. Bristol Myers. Comtrex. BMCE 9703 Tina Capsules :30. 1978 (Box 26)
        - 420. Daniel & Charles. Comtrex. 4 Spots. See Enclosed List. 1978 (Box 26)
        - 421. Film power #1018. Comtrex. 4 Spots. See Enclosed List. 1979 (Box 26)
        - 422. Comtrex. 14 spots. See Enclosed List. Undated (Box 26)
        - 423. Daniel & Charles. Bristol Myers. Comtrex. BMCE 9013 Summer Cold Tablets :30. 1979 (Box 26)
        - 424. Bristol Myers. Comtrex Historical Reel. 11-30 Sec. Spots. See Enclosed List. 1979 (Box 26)
        - 425. Bristol Myers. Comtrex Historical Reel. 11-30 Sec. Spots. See Enclosed List. 1979 (Box 26)
        - 426. Film power #1018. Comtrex. 4 Spots. See Enclosed List. 1979 (Box 26)
        - 427. Bristol Myers. Comtrex. BMCE 9353 Almost Forgot Ingrid III :30. 1979 (Box 26)
        - 428. Daniel & Charles. Bristol Myers. Comtrex. BMCE 9983 Black and White :30. 1979 (Box 26)
      - Comtrex (continued), 1979-1980 (Box 27)
        - 429. Daniel & Charles. Bristol Myers. Comtrex. BMCE 9303 Sliding Medicine Chest :30. 1979 (Box 27)
        - 430. Daniel & Charles. Bristol Myers. Comtrex. 6-30 Sec. Spots. See Enclosed List. 1979 (Box 27)
        - 431. Daniel & Charles. Bristol Myers. Comtrex. BMCE 9813 Nyquil/Chest/Rucker :30. 1979 (Box 27)
        - 432. Daniel & Charles. Bristol Myers. Comtrex. BMCE 9333 Last Cold/NT II :30. 1979 (Box 27)
        - 433. Daniel & Charles. Bristol Myers. Comtrex. BMCE 9333 Last/NT cold II":30. 1979 (Box 27)
        - 434. Daniel & Charles. Comtrex. BMCE 9803 Bayer/Chest/Rucker :30. 1979 (Box 27)
        - 435. Bristol Myers. Comtrex. BMCE 9793 :30. 1979 (Box 27)
        - 436. Daniel & Charles. Bristol Myers. Comtrex. BMCE 8753 Dristan/Chest/Rucker :30. 1979 (Box 27)
        - 437. Film power. Comtrex. Harper :60/:30; Harlan :30. 1979 (Box 27)
        - 438. Daniel & Charles. Bristol Myers. Comtrex. BMCE 9143 Tina Sloan :30; BMCE 9153 Ann Eurr :30; BMCE 9163 Sauntra Sharp :30. 1979 (Box 27)
        - 439. Daniel & Charles. Bristol Myers. Comtrex. BMCE 9213 I Almost Forgot Rev. 2 :30. 1979 (Box 27)
        - 440. Daniel & Charles. Comtrex. BMCE 8753 Dristan/Chest/Rucker :30; BMCE 9813 Nyquil/Chest/Rucker :30; Bayer/Chest/Rucker :30. 1979 (Box 27)
        - 441. Daniel & Charles. Bristol Myers. Comtrex. Last Cold Demo Opening #1 #2. 2-30 Sec Spots. 1979 (Box 27)
        - 442. 4 Spots. See Enclosed List. 1980 (Box 27)
        - 443. Bristol Myers. Comtrex. BMCE 9213 I Almost Forgot Rev. 2 :30. 1980 (Box 27)
        - 444. Bristol Myers. Daniel & Charles. Comtrex. BMCE 0393 Last Cold/CD Rev. II BMCE 0403 Last Cold/DN Rev. II :30. 1980 (Box 27)
      - Comtrex (continued), 1980-1981 (Box 28)
        - 445. Bristol Myers. Comtrex. 19-30 sec. Spots. See Enclosed List. 1980 (Box 28)
        - 446. Daniel & Charles. Bristol Myers. Comtrex. 4 Spots. See Enclosed List. 1980 (Box 28)
        - 447. Bristol Myers. Comtrex. BMCE 0503 Almost Forgot/Single :30. 1980 (Box 28)
        - 448. Daniel & Charles. Bristol Myers. Comtrex. BMCE 0443; BMCE 0473; BMCE 0463 :30 Each. 1980 (Box 28)
        - 449. Daniel & Charles. Bristol Myers. Comtrex. 7-30 sec Spots. See Enclosed List. 1980 (Box 28)
        - 450. Daniel & Charles. Bristol Myers. Comtrex. BMCE 0271 I Almost Forgot/Bayer :30; BMCE 0813 I Almost Forgot/Tylenol/Rev 8 :30. 1980 (Box 28)
        - 451. Daniel & Charles. Bristol Myers. Comtrex. BMCE 0721 I almost Forgot/Bayer :10; BMCE 0813 I almost forgot/tylenol/rev.8 :30. 1980 (Box 28)
        - 452. Daniel & Charles. Bristol Myers. Comtrex. 4 spots. See Enclosed List. 1980 (Box 28)
        - 453. Bristol Myers. Comtrex. BMCE 0531 Battle for the ballot/ID :30. 1980 (Box 28)
        - 454. Daniel & Charles. Comtrex. 3 Demo Spots. 1980 (Box 28)
        - 455. Daniel & Charles. Bristol Myers. Comtrex. BMCE 1243 too much/rev :30. 1981 (Box 28)
        - 456. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Comtrex. BMCE 1183 Comtrex does":30. 1981 (Box 28)
        - 457. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Comtrex. BMCE 1183 Comtrex does :30. 1981 (Box 28)
        - 458. Daniel & Charles. Bristol Myers. Comtrex. BMCE 1223 Rain :30; BMCE 1203 EX-User :30; BMCE 1193 Too Much :30. 1981 (Box 28)
        - 459.Daniel & Charles. DJM 4086. Comtrex. 6-30 sec spots. See Enclosed List. 1981 (Box 28)
        - 460. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Comtrex. BMCE 2433 good strong medicine :30. 1981 (Box 28)
        - 461. Daniel & Charles. Bristol Myers. Comtrex. BMCE 1053 Last Cold/DB :30; BMCE 1093 Last Cold/DC :30; BMCE 1043 Last Cold/tc Rev :30. 1981 (Box 28)
      - Comtrex (continued), 1981-1982 (Box 29)
        - 462. Daniel & Charles. Bristol Myers. Comtrex. BMCE 1253 Last Cold/TC 2 :30; BMCE 1243 Last Cold/DB 2 :30; BMCE 1263 Last Cold/DC :30. 1981 (Box 29)
        - 463. Daniel & Charles. Bristol Myers. Comtrex. BMCE 1253 Last Cold/TC 2 :30; BMCE 1243 Last Cold/DB 2 :30; BMCE 1263 Last Cold/DC :30. 1981 (Box 29)
        - 464. Daniel & Charles. Bristol Myers. Comtrex. BMCE 1193 too much :30. 1981 (Box 29)
        - 465. Daniel & Charles. Bristol Myers. Comtrex Nighttime. BMKN 1153 Hush/rev #4; BMKN 1173 Hush/rev #5; BMKN 1233 Hush/rev #5 Alt. 1981 (Box 29)
        - 466. Daniel & Charles. Comtrex. BMKN 1233 Hush #5 Alt rev. :30. 1981 (Box 29)
        - 467. Daniel & Charles. Comtrex. cold :30. 1981 (Box 29)
        - 468. Daniel & Charles. Bristol Myers. Comtrex. BMCE 1053 last cold/db :30; BMCE 1093 last cold/dc:30; BMCE 1043 last cold/tc :30. 1981 (Box 29)
        - 469. Bristol Myers. Comtrex. BMCE 0823 Basketball :30; BMCE 0793 Movie :30; BMCE 0773 Comtrex Can Vers. A :30. 1981 (Box 29)
        - 470. Bristol Myers. Comtrex. BMCE 0673 I almost forgot rev. 6/Bayer :30; BMCE 0653 movie/tylenol :30; BMCE 0823 basketball :30. 1981 (Box 29)
        - 471. Daniel & Charles.Comtrex. Comtrex does :30; last cold/cd :30; less/more :30. 1981 (Box 29)
        - 472. Daniel & Charles. Bristol Myers. Comtrex. little cold :30. 1981 (Box 29)
        - 473. Daniel & Charles. Comtrex. 4 spots. See Enclosed List. 1981 (Box 29)
        - 474. Bristol Myers. Comtrex. BMCE 1963 last cold/dc :30. 1981 (Box 29)
        - 475. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Comtrex. BMCE 2933 will relieve it/whole cold. 1982 (Box 29)
        - 476. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Maximum Strength Comtrex. BMCE 2153 Americas cold maximum strength :30. 1982 (Box 29)
        - 477. Bristol Myers. Comtrex. BMCE 2123 America's Cold :30. 1982 (Box 29)
        - 478. Bristol Myers. Comtrex. BMCE 1943 All Competitive Labels :30. 1981 (Box 29)
      - Comtrex (continued), 1982-1983 (Box 30)
        - 479. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Comtrex. new relief is here :30; internal dialogue :30. 1982 (Box 30)
        - 480. Bristol Myers. Comtrex. BMCE 1873 Basketball/Bayer II; BMCE 1883 movie/tylenol II :30 each. Undated (Box 30)
        - 481. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Comtrex. BMCE 2893 Singer-10 Symptoms; BMCE 2943 Coach-10Symptoms; BMCE 2933 Negative II :30 each. 1982 (Box 30)
        - 482. Bristol Myers. Comtrex. BMCE 2963 Comtrex Does whole Cold :30. 1982 (Box 30)
        - 483. Bristol Myers. Comtrex. BMCE 2963 Comtrex Does/whole Cold :30. 1982 (Box 30)
        - 484. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Comtrex. BMCE 2933 will relieve it/whole cold :30. 1982 (Box 30)
        - 485. Bristol Myers. Comtrex. BMCE 2123 Americas cold :30. 1982 (Box 30)
        - 486. Bristol Myers. Comtrex. BMCE 1963 last cold/CL :30; BMCE 1893 Comtrex can :30. Undated (Box 30)
        - 487. Bristol Myers. Comtrex. BMCE 2193 Internal Dialogue :30. 1982 (Box 30)
        - 488. Bristol Myers. Comtrex. BMCE 3733 Could We Improve :30. 1983 (Box 30)
        - 489. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Comtrex. BMCE 3763 Husband And Wife Rev I :30. 1983 (Box 30)
        - 490. Bristol Myers. Comtrex. 6-30 sec spots. See Enclosed List. 1983 (Box 30)
        - 491. Daniel & Charles. Bristol Myers. Comtrex. BMCE 0413 last cold/cd rev III :30; BMCE 0423 Last Cold/DN Rev. III :30. Undated (Box 30)
        - 492. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Comtrex. BMCE 3743 Husband and Wife :30. Undated (Box 30)
        - 493. Bristol Myers. Comtrex. BMCE 3563 long day :30; BMCE 3542 Better now, Better Later :30. 1983 (Box 30)
        - 494. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Comtrex. BMCE 3703 I came this close :30; BMCE 3723 That’s all/question :30. 1983 (Box 30)
        - 495. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Comtrex. BMCE 3803 That's All/questions rev. 2 :30; BMCE 3813 That's all/pool out :30. 1983 (Box 30)
      - Comtrex (continued), 1983-1985 (Box 31)
        - 496. Bristol Myers. Comtrex. BMCE 3733 Could We Improve :30. 1983 (Box 31)
        - 497. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Comtrex A/S. BMAC 4043 Radio. 1984 (Box 31)
        - 498. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Comtrex A/S. BMAC 4013 Botanical Gardens rev. 1984 (Box 31)
        - 499. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Comtrex A/S. BMAC 4063 attention BMAC 4053 A/S. 1984 (Box 31)
        - 500. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Comtrex. Bristol Myers. 8:17 Cold. 1984 (Box 31)
        - 501. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Comtrex. BMCE 4963 That's all/questions again Vers. 1 :30; BMCE 4973 That's all/questions again Vers. 2 Magic :30. 1984 (Box 31)
        - 502. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Comtrex A/S. BMAC 4053 A/S Alt. II New. 1984 (Box 31)
        - 503. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Comtrex A/S. BMAC 4063 Attention; BMAC 4053 A/s. 1984 (Box 31)
        - 504. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Comtrex. BMCE 4943 That's all/recording studio :30; BMCE 4963 That's all/questions again Vers. 1 :30. 1984 (Box 31)
        - 505. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Comtrex. BMCE 4893 that's all/coupon. 1984 (Box 31)
        - 506. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Comtrex A/S. Transformation rev; Botanical Garden. 1984 (Box 31)
        - 507. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Comtrex A/S. BMAC 4043 Radio Alt. 1984 (Box 31)
        - 508. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Comtrex A/S. BMAC 4023 Transformation rev.; BMAC 4013 Botanical Garden. 1984 (Box 31)
        - 509. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Comtrex. BMCE 4943 That's all/recording studio :30; BMCE 4963 That's All question again Vers. 1984 (Box 31)
        - 510. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Comtrex A/S. BMAC 4053 A/S Alt. II New. 1984 (Box 31)
        - 511. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Comtrex. BMCE 5233 Hotel Manager Rev. I :30. 1985 (Box 31)
      - Comtrex (continued), 1985 (Box 32)
        - 512. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Comtrex. BMCE 5993 That's all/Dept. Store :30. 1985 (Box 32)
        - 513. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Comtrex. BMCE 5993 That's all/Dept. Store :30. 1985 (Box 32)
        - 514. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Comtrex. BMCE 5103 Honeymoon :30; BMCE 5113 Store :30. 1985 (Box 32)
        - 515. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Comtrex. BMCE 5233 Hotel Manager rev. I :30. 1985 (Box 32)
        - 516. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Comtrex. BMCE 5063 Bride :30. 1985 (Box 32)
        - 517. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Comtrex A/S. BMAC 5103 Tennis :30; BMAC 5113 An Allergy Profile :30. 1985 (Box 32)
        - 518. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Comtrex. BMCE 5063 Bride :30. 1985 (Box 32)
        - 519. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Comtrex. BMCE 5103 Honeymoon :30; BMCE 5113 store :30. 1985 (Box 32)
        - 520. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Comtrex. BMCE 5243 That’s all/dept. Store rev. :30; BMCE 5255 That's all/Dept. Store Rev. :15. 1985 (Box 32)
        - 521. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Comtrex. BMCE 5075 Bride Alt. IV :15. 1985 (Box 32)
        - 522. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Comtrex. BMCE 5083 Hotel Manager :30. 1985 (Box 32)